drop this one here is the cdance 2.01 so this is obviously going to be the most expensive generation
nice okay this one is good I like that sound effects at the end I don't like
like this part here that's unrealistic but there's so much happening here it doesn't really matter
too much in my opinion but I don't love that one and then we just are waiting for this one to
generate like this is cdance mini okay mini is just not working here that one is not working we
could include mini doesn't work for this this one is probably the fast one I would imagine
yet so this is fast in the correct dimensions
okay this one's nice because this is probably the best one so far all the layers are
animating nicely this animation is changing obviously different each time and you could
probably go back into the prompt and just describe this if you wanted to like if you've got an idea
I don't mind that to be fair it doesn't have to be super realistic it kind of just has to look
cool the sound effects be good but yeah as you can see like easy peasy works pretty well happy
with that I will say the only caveat to generating at 720p is you do lose some of the details
of the text here you can fix this with 1080 or you basically potentially generate an image that
doesn't really have tiny text and you're going to get that problem across any video model not just
like this specific example of collage animations like if I have text that small on an image and
it goes into a video model they will all struggle to do that unless you're generating like on the
cdance 4k model which is expensive so I would use that if you really really have to you know maybe
it's like something going on client work or it's like you know you need the top top top quality
then use 4k but the only problem is is then you'll get you'll get a different generation it
might not be the one that you want actually fuck it I'll generate one in 4k if I've got enough
credits I'm running out of credits how many I don't know how many credits that equals 4k 5 so
not too much cdance 2.0 4k now generate the 4k one and see how all that comes out it's probably
going to take a while it don't take sort of a couple of minutes as for sure it takes a few minutes
right so these are both generated right now this is the cdance 2.0 720 quality nice
not too bad but you see the animation that don't like that so kind of worked but again if we compare
that to the fast version no better than the fast version in my opinion and then finally now
we've got the 4k one don't recommend this don't know how many because 6000 credits I don't know
how much that costs I know it's usually like one dollar a second nice animation is nice
it's just the clarity I'm just gonna download this and just show you the like clarity of the
text this is the only reason why I would probably use this model is if I need the text clarity because
it does just look if we look here like it's actually held the clarity of the text there like look how
small that text is designed in California QC pass inspected that look how that date there look like
you cannot get that on any other model do I think the animation is much better than the others
not at all not at all to be honest all of the like the start of them are all very similar in terms
of they do the job of putting that on and then they've all done the animation kind of different but
the 4k does look nice it does look nice but super expensive to run but overall I think this is
really fun and easy to do if you have any questions or you discover anything new or have your own
really good prompt that you'd like to share then drop them in the comments but other than that have
a nice week and I'll see you in the next video